You guys are not
going to believe this.
I just got off the phone
with my agent.
Oh, my God!
I'm sorry. Too soon.
You go.
Okay.
I got nominated for my part
on Days of Our Lives.
Oh, Joey!
Good for you!
Congratulations.
I can't believe
you're nominated
for an Emmy.
No, no.
Soap Opera Digest Award.
No. I'm up for a Soapie.
Honey. Is that something
you're making up?
No, no, no, it's real
and it has been since 1998.
Hey, Rach, Rach.
I'm up for a Soapie.
( gasps )
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
That is, like, the third
most-prestigious
soap opera award there is.
Thank you.
Well, I guess
now we know
who I'm taking
to the awards.
Oh, stop that.
Don't kid about that.
Will all the stars be there?
Many are scheduled
to appear.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, I can't go.
I'm going to be
too nervous.
Okay, I'll go.
No!
You're getting married.
This is all I have.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
And it was Ernst Molbrat
who first hypothesized
that the velociraptor,
when threatened
would expand its collar
and emit a high-pitched noise
to frighten off its predator.
Yes, Mr. Lewis?
What kind of noise?
Just a high-pitched,
intimidating noise.
Like how?
Well, we,
we don't know for sure
but in my head, it, it sounded
something like this...
Uh...
( shrill falsetto squeaking):
Ah-ah-ahh! Ah-ah-ahh!
Ah!
Of course,
this is just conjecture.
( voice breaking ):
Okay, that's...
that's all for today.
Oh, Mr. Morse
can I see you for a moment?
Yes, sir?
Mr. Morse, I need
to talk to you
about your midterm exam.
I'm afraid
I-I had to fail you.
Why?
Well, you need 60% to pass.
What'd I get?
Seven.
That's not so good.
No, no, it's not.
What happened there, Ned?
Well, maybe you can
cut me some slack.
I'm sort of in love.
Well, I'm sorry,
but that's, that's
really not my problem.
I'm in love with you.
Well, that brings me
in the loop a little.
See, that's why I did
so bad on this test.
I'm having a hard
time concentrating.
When you're up there...
and you're teaching
and your face
gets all serious
it looks so good
and when you wear
that tight little
turtleneck sweater...
Okay.
Ned, uh...
I, uh... I'm your teacher.
I'm sorry. You're...
You're a student,
and I, and I like women
in spite of what
may be written
on the backs
of some of these chairs.
Oh, my God.
That guy at the counter is
totally checking you out.
Really?
My God,
he's really cute.
Go for it.
Phoebe, I'm engaged.
I'm just saying, get
his number just in case.
No, if Chandler
is in an accident and can't
perform sexually, you know
then he would want
you to take a lover
to satisfy the needs that
he can no longer fulfill.
Hi, I'm...
Oh. Could I just
tell you something?
Um... I'm very flattered,
but, uh... I'm engaged.
Wow, uh...
This is kind of embarrassing.
I was actually coming over
to talk to your friend.
Well, you should
be embarrassed.
I thought you knew
I was looking at you.
I did, but that
was really fun.
And the winner is...
Joey Tribbiani.
Oh!
Oh.
Wow. I...
honestly never expected this.
I, uh, I haven't even
prepared a speech
but, uh...
I'd like to thank
my parents
who've always
been there for me.
I'd also like
to thank my friends--
Chandler... Monica...
Phoebe, Rachel.
I'm fourth?
Geez!
Look at you with your
little maple syrup award.
Yeah, may-maybe you don't
tell anyone about this.
What?
No, it's not a big deal.
I do that, too--
with my shampoo bottle.
Really?
Yeah.
What award are you
practicing for?
Grammy.
Best New Artist.
Ooh.
Oh, hey, listen-- the
Soapies people called today
and I also get
present an award.
Oh, that's great.
Yeah.
So you'll definitely
get onstage
even if you don't win.
Y-y-you don't think
I'm going to win?
But of course I do.
Oh. Well...
But, you know,
Favorite Returning Character
is a tough category, Joey.
I mean, you're up
against the guy
who survived his own cremation.
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
No, I know I
might not win
but it's just...
I've never even been
nominated before.
I want it so much.
Well, you know,
and you'll probably get it
but you should probably
start practicing
your-your
"gracious loser" face.
You know, when, like,
the cameras are on you
and you want
to look disappointed
but also
that your colleague
deserved to win,
you know?
So it's sort of like...
( gasps )
Good.
You know?
You practice losing
at the Grammys, too?
Oh, no. At the Grammys,
I always win.
Ah.
Oh, hey!
Hey.
Oh, how'd your date
go with Jake?
Great.
We couldn't keep our eyes
off each other all night
and then, every
once in a while
he'd kind of
just lean over
and stroke my hair and
then touch my neck.
Okay, stop it, Phoebe,
you're getting me all tingly.
All I could
think of was
"Is he going
to kiss me?
Is he going to kiss me?"
And did he?
I'm a lady, Monica.
I don't kiss and tell
but this hickey
speaks for itself.
Okay, okay.
I got it. I got it.
I just like him so much
that I just feel
like I've had ten drinks today--
and I've only had six.
Oh. You know,
I haven't had that feeling
since I first started
going out with Chandler.
Well. I'm never going to
have that feeling again, am I?
You sound like a guy.
No, a guy would be saying
"I'm never going to get
to sleep with anyone else."
Oh, my God, I'm never going to
get to sleep with anyone else.
I've been so busy
planning the wedding
that I forgot about all the
things I'd be giving up.
I'm never going to have
a first kiss again.
You'll have a last kiss.
Can I ask you something?
You ever had a guy
have a crush on you?
Is that why you wanted
to tie my tie?
There's this kid
in my class
who said he's
in love with me.
Whoa.
Whoa, what?
Ross has a boyfriend.
I do... I do not
have a boyfriend.
There's a guy in
one of my classes
who, who has a crush on me.
Really?
Yeah.
I don't know. I mean,
last year Elizabeth.
Now, now this kid.
What-what, what is it?
Am I giving out some kind
of a... sexy-professor vibe?
Not right now.
The point is,
my natural charisma
has made him fail his midterm.
See, now I feel
bad for the kid.
I had a crush on a teacher once
and it was so hard, you know.
I couldn't concentrate
and I blushed every time
he looked at me.
Come on, you remember what
it's like to be 19 and in love.
Okay.
Guess I can cut him some slack.
Yeah.
So how'd you
get over that teacher?
I didn't.
I got under him.
Problem solved.
Bye, Phoebe.
Okay, bye.
All right.
Bye.
( sighs )
We said good-bye
at the door
so as not to flaunt
our new love.
Oh, Phoebe
it's okay, you don't
have to tiptoe around me.
I've been thinking about it
and... you know what?
I'm okay about not having
that new relationship feeling.
I miss you already!
( loudly ):
I miss you, too!
See, that's what I mean.
I mean, that,
that's great
but I wouldn't trade in
what I have for that.
I mean, I'm going
to be with Chandler
for the rest of my life
and that's what makes me happy.
Hey, sweetie, come here.
Come sit down.
Hey, Phoebe and I
were just talking
about how our relationship
is deep and meaningful.
It really is,
don't you think?
Oh, totally.
Pull my finger.
This is it, this is it.
This is my category.
Do you have
your speech?
Yeah, got my speech.
You got your
"gracious loser" face?
Yeah.
Very nice.
Now, remember, if you
win, you have to hug me.
You hug me.
Okay.
Can I squeeze your ass?
On TV?
Yeah.
Okay!
In the category of Favorite
Returning Male Character
the nominees are...
John Wheeler
from General Hospital
Gavin Graham
from The Young and the Restless
Duncan Harrington from Passions
and Joey Tribbiani
from Days of our Lives
and the Soapie goes to...
Gavin Graham
from The Young and the Restless.
What the...?!
( music playing )
for Favorite Supporting Actress
is Joey Tribbiani
from Days of Our Lives.
Whoo!
( applause and music )
( in a monotone ):
Any one of
the brilliant actresses
nominated for this award tonight
deserves to take it home.
Unfortunately, only one can.
( scoffing softly )
The nominees for Favorite
Supporting Actress are...
from Passions, Erin Gough...
from One Life to Live,
Mary Lauren Bishop...
( cutting off applause):
from All My Children,
Sarah Renee...
and from Days of Our Lives,
Jessica Ashley.
And the winner is...
Jessica Ashley
from Days of Our Lives.
Oh, uh, unfortunately
Jessica couldn't be
with us tonight
so I'll be accepting
this award
on her behalf.
And I'm sure that Jessica...
would like to thank my parents
who always
believed in me.
She'd also like to thank
my friends
Chandler, Monica, Ross,
Phoebe and Rachel
who's sitting right there.
( microphone goes dead )
Joey, why did we have
to rush out of there so fast?
Rach, we had to get
out of there because...
look what I won! Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Oh, my God, you
stole her award.
No, no, oh, no.
I'm accepting it on her behalf.
Well... Joey, I don't
think you know
what "behalf" means.
Sure I do.
It's a verb,
as in "I behalf'n it."
Joey...
you have got
to take this back.
Why?
I should've won one,
and I really wanted it.
She didn't even care enough
to come to the thing.
It could also be a Grammy.
No, Joey.
Come on, Rach.
No one saw me take it.
There was a whole table
full of them.
Do you really want an award
that you didn't win?
No. I want an award I did win
but nobody's given me
any of those.
Plus, okay, Rach,
if I put it up there-- right?--
when people come over,
they'll see it
and they'll think I won it.
Joey, it says "Best
Supporting Actress."
I can scratch that right off.
Joey, no, this is wrong.
You have to take it back.
Okay? You don't want
to win an award this way.
You're very talented
and someday you're going
to win one of these for real
and that one is going
to mean something.
All right.
All right?
Thank you.
I'll take it back tomorrow.
If I can't have it,
you can't have it.
( grunts angrily )
Professor Geller?
Yes, Mr. Lewis,
how can I help you?
I know I didn't do well
on my midterms and stuff, but...
I was kind of hoping
you could change my grade.
And why exactly
would I do that?
'Cause I'm in love with you.
What?
Yeah. I'm all...
in love with you and stuff.
So could you change my grade?
No!
Well, why not?
You changed Ned's grade.
Well, that's different, okay?
Because he was actually
in love with me.
No, he's not.
He's totally yanking your chain.
He's done this
with three other teachers.
What?
He's got a girlfriend.
I can't believe someone
would do that for a grade.
I know. It's awful.
I love you.
Hey, have you
seen Chandler?
No. Why?
'Cause I just
keep thinking
about all these things
that I'm not going to have,
and it's freaking me out.
I don't know what
to do about it.
Okay, don't sweat it.
Chandler is nowhere around
so go ahead,
get it out of your system.
That guy's cute.
Phoebe, come on,
I'm serious.
I've just got to talk
to him about all this.
That is the last thing
you want to do.
Why?
Because you're marrying him.
You got to help me
out here, Pheebs.
All right,
I've never been engaged
and I've never
really been married
but I can only tell you
what my mother told me.
Whenever you have
doubts or fears
or anxieties
about a relationship
do not communicate them
to your husband.
So, I'm not supposed to
share my doubts and fears
with the guy I'm
going to spend the
rest of my life with?
That is correct.
Yes, you're supposed
to take all that stuff
and put it in a little box
in your mind
and then lock it up tight.
Your mother told you this?
Yes.
The woman that got married
a bunch of times
and killed herself
when you were 13?
Oh, my God, you're right.
All right, go.
Go tell Chandler.
Hurry, before it's too late.
Wait! No!
Does this also mean
that putting out
doesn't get you love?
I cannot believe I'm going
to meet Jessica Ashley.
Wait, wait. Please...
be cool, okay?
I work with this woman.
Okay, I'm totally cool.
Okay.
Come in.
Hey, Jessica.
Hey, Jess.
Uh, this is my friend Rachel.
Hi.
What's up?
Uh, listen,
here's your trophy.
I accepted it for you.
Oh, my God, I won?
Do you have any idea
what this means?
Wow, that-that's it?
You're not going...
you're not going to put it
on your shelf or anything?
No. I try to save that
for real awards.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
Hmm...
Take it back?
Absolutely.
Yeah, you do.
Honey?
Hmm?
As we get closer
to the wedding
is there anything that you'd
like to talk about or share?
Okay, well, I think
the centerpieces are too big.
You're wrong.
The centerpieces are fine.
Do you ever get scared at all?
Kind of. They're really big.
I mean, does it ever
freak you out that-that...
you're never going to be
with anybody new again?
What?
Just... I love you so much.
It's just that
sometimes it bothers me
that I'm never going
to have that feeling...
you know, when you meet someone
for the first time
and it's new and exciting.
You know that rush?
No.
Now, see, when I
first meet somebody
it's, uh, it's mostly panic,
anxiety and a...
great deal of sweating.
Okay, but, all right,
you're a guy.
Does it not freak you out
that you're never going
to sleep with anybody else?
Sleeping with somebody new.
Anxiety, panic and, I'm afraid,
even more sweating.
Even with me?
I was dangerously dehydrated
during the first six months
of our relationship.
Look...
for me, the rush is knowing
that we are going to be together
for the rest of our lives.
Really?
Well, yeah.
But now that I know that
you're having these thoughts
we're back to panic, anxiety,
and, uh
I'm definitely going to need
some kind of sports drink.
Come here.
Sweetie, you don't
have to worry.
No. Besides, you know what?
I'm going to have a lot
of new things with you:
the first time we buy a house,
our first kid
our first grandkid.
Water! Water! Water!
Uh, Mr. Morse, can I speak
to you for a moment?
That was a great
lecture today.
Did you get a little haircut?
Mm-hmm, yeah, yeah.
Do you like it?
Do you love it?
I just want you to know that
I'm changing your grade back.
What? Why?
Because I know what you're
trying to pull here, okay?
It's not going to work.
I'm not trying
to pull anything.
Look, I love you, dude.
You know what?
I'm not even going to
talk about this, okay?
This little thing is over.
I know you have
a girlfriend.
Okay? Yeah, and I know
about the other professors.
How do you think that
makes me feel, Ned?
You used me!
You don't love me,
and you never did!
Ah, Professor Winston,
Professor Frederickson.
I'll be right with you.
Don't make this worse,
and I'll give you a "C."
Shall we?
Rach?
I'll be out
in a second.
Mmm.
It's just so unexpected.
( laughing ):
I... I, uh...
Well, it's... I'll tell you,
it's just such an honor
to just be nominated...
for a Nobel prize.
And, you know, to win one
for a massage, oh...
especially after having just won
a Tony award for Best Actress...
We have to go.
Our reservations are at 8:00.
In Reservations at 8:00...
by Neil Simon.
Thank you, thank you, Neil.
Thank you for the words.
Okay, honey, you can
finish this later.
We're going to be late.
We got to go.
No, please, don't
play the music.
I just have
one more thing.
Okay.
Live from New York,
it's Saturday Night!